

Graphic Design + Marketing Specialist

Jenna Howard

- j.m.howard30@gmail.com
- Macon, GA
- jhoward.design
- **%** (478) 719-0474

Profile

With 10 years in digital & traditional marketing, I specialize in turning ideas into powerful visual content. My expertise includes brand awareness, visual storytelling, graphic design, & client engagement. I've served a range of clients, ensuring each brand's voice resonates with their target.

Skills

- PowerPoint
- FIGMA
- MailChimp
- Adobe Photoshop
- Facebook
- Adobe Illustrator
- Google Ads + Analytics
- Adobe PremierePro

Employment

2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Transformed complex concepts into compelling PowerPoint presentations for internal training & client-facing needs. Oversaw social media strategy & engagement. Developed email campaigns that netted \$30k in direct revenue. Produced a range of promotional materials & led digital marketing initiatives.

2019 - now Freelance Graphic Designer

Overhauled client branding & content planning. Designed, developed, & maintained client websites, Google Business pages, & social media accounts. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced brochures, emails, menus, product photography, signage, & digital advertising. Reported client analytics.

2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

Education

2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication